For the purposes of the Sunshine app, this information is purely theoretical.
In fact, you'll really only need to consider this later,
when you're adding things like Sensor or LocationListeners. Until then,
the default components will handle much of this behavior for
you. In any case, now that you understand the lifecycle and
the way the system handles exiting your app, when it needs its resources.
You should hopefully understand why Exit or Quit buttons in Android apps serve
no practical purpose. At most, you can call finish on an activity and
it will get torn down instantly. That's actually exactly what happens when
you use a simple hits back from within their activity.
If you're still not convinced, check out the video in the instructor notes.
Where I explain my reasoning with a little more, color.